listography.com 2019-12-01

# listography: privacy policy

## listography privacy policy

### we do not spam or sell email addresses.

listography.com is a an online service that allows members to self-create personal profiles that can be linked together through a chosen network of "favorites" (links to other user's Listographies). Listography members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them. Listography allows our users to share a broad range of lists that each user is in control of creating, ranging from recommendations, auto-biographical, top tens, wishlists, photo lists, to do lists, etc. Users control all aspects of content on their Listography Page: profile photo, list topics and lists, "about" text, personal links, photos in photo lists, etc. 

listography.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the listography.com service. listography.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: gender and age. All information is kept private except information the user chooses to display on their homepage. At a future date, birthday reminders (month and day only) may be displayed. 

listography.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. User Profile information including members' pictures and chosen user names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the listography.com community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting others to join listography.com, to add users to members' favorites' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of invites, adding favorites, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed. To facilitate searching for others within the service, listography.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name or email address. We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or updates regarding the service. 

### Invites

listography.com members can invite others to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. listography.com stores the email addresses that members provide temporarily in our log files. listography.com does not sell any email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations or invitation reminders. Requests can be made to remove email addresses from our database via the Contact Page. 

### Use of Cookies

listography.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from listography.com in order to use most functions on the site. 

### Links

listography.com contains links to other websites. listography.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information on listography.com. 

### Public Forums

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information it is accessible to the public and can in turn be used to send you unsolicited communications. For example, users control which links they choose that relate to them. Do not choose links that you do not want in the public. Do not display information anywhere on your Listography Page that you wouldn't want outside viewers to know or see, i.e. : address, phone number, email address, IM name, and other identifying information. 

### Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

listography.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features under the Settings Page. 

### Security

listography.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. listography.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information listography.com Collects

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, listography.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by listography.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the listography.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. listography.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of listography.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. 

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect and how we use it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you by posting a notice on our Website for 30 days.
